Fixed & Synced by bozxphd. Enjoy The Flick.
Hey Kia.
What is this?
It's a party... enjoy yourself
I'll just he hack.
It's a Wedding not a seminar.
Come on, enjoy yourself!
I'll just he hack.
Don't feel shy my dear...
Take this.
Loosen up and enjoy yourself.
Take it.
- Let's enjoy?
- Sorry...
- I have my chums.
- Excuse me?
Chums? Periods?
Menstrual cycle?
No problem! Stay free!
Enjoy "Y!
Mrs. Aurora. Axon...
I hope you ale happy with
the wedding arrangements.
Please don't say that...
Can't you see how much
everyone is enjoying?
Forget about everyone...
Look how happy 0111 son is!
You: daughter is lovely.
She will take good care of him.
MI. Kapoor, it's true...
behind every successful
there has to be a woman.
The two of us are
living proof of that!
Today he is VP, tomorrow
he will be President...
then CEO, Chairman.
How can a man work fol
16-1101115 a day...
without a good support system?
My daughter-in-law will
5011 out this fool's life.
Thank you!
Hey Kia.
What axe you Going hem'?
Go enjoy yourself.
Hello? Hello?
Hello?
How can I enjoy myself?
My best friend is dying!
Today her happiness, dreams,
identity, independence...
Basically it's her last day
of being alive.
From tomorrow she will
be a support...
Like a pillar...
Ya, ya pillar.
Sure, that's important too.
But the world will always say...
Wow! What a building!
Who talks about the poor pillar'?
No, no I like marriage.
It's a nice concept.
But Why should I spend my
life with someone
who after 40 years will look
into my eyes and say...
Thank you fol being my pillar!
Enjoy, enjoy.
You ok?
Sorry!
You Want something?
Ma!
I Want my mom!
Yes Minn'!?
Can you get this gentleman...
- his Ma?
- Excuse me?
Mom?
Kabir.
Kia.
Mom...
would hold my hand really tight
during take off & landing...
Like this...
She was very scared of flying.
Was?
It's been 10 years
since she passed away.
Today is her birthday...
That's Why...
something happened,
something flashed,
something crashed...
and you received this gift.
What gift?
The gift of seeing a boy cry
live in flout of a gill.
You're happy light... -
that your mom was horn?
Then why cry on her birthday'?
Celebrate!
Happy birthday Aunty!
Dad's alive right?
Ya.
Are you sad that he is'?
No... he's OK.
Mama's boy!
Mama's boy does not
like his Daddy?
It's not that.
It's tough...
to like MI. Bhansal is tough.
My dad is Kumar Bansal
Bansal?
The builder'?
I'm already liking you!
You're the son of the man
who owns half of Delhi!
The most expensive scotch!
Double, on the locks
please!
This is the problem with
low cost airlines.
You can't tell the rich
from the poor.
Everyone travels economy.
So'?
MI. Kabir Bansal...
You were in Chandigarh
to buy Chandigarh'?
No.
My friend had a break-up...
I was there for rnoral support.
Cheers!
To you: friend's freedom.
So...
Having issues with dad?
You Want to transform his
business with your new ideas...
but he's not agreeing.
Corn-wt?
He Wants to show you
he's still the boss.
The usual problem with
big business families.
First produce a son
to takeover the business.
When the son is ready
to takeover,
the father is not ready
to handover!
The usual "father-son" friction
I totally get it
I have no interest in
my dad's business.
What?
And before you order another
double on the rocks...
I Want to share a big
truth with you.
What?
This expensive scotch
of yours...
I can't afford it.
Are you Kumar Bausal's stepson?
No, the one & only son.
But if I have no interest in
dad's business,
to have interest in
his money...
not cool, right?
So What do you do than?
Why?
Do I have to do something?
Yes of course!
Why do you need to do anything?
Whether you are interested
in dad's money...
or not...
after he's gone R's
all yams anyway.
- What do you do?
- I work at Marion.
What do you do there'?
I'm a Marketing Manager.
What plans after that?
After that, in a couple of years
I'll be Vice President.
After that?
I will he CEO.
WOW!
With such clarity...
every dream comes true.
- We should have a dream in life.
- Correct!
OI of coulee...
a dad!
Yes, I have a dad.
But even I have a dream.
- Don't tell me!
- Okay I Won't tell you.
Okay tell!
Because actually I really
want to know...
When someone has everything...
What would his dream he?
Tell...
I Want to he like my mom.
Excuse me?
I...
want to be like my mother.
My Plume!
When-is my phone?
Give me your number.
I just called to say
I am not a "She", I am a "He".
What?
I'm not gay.
I don't Want to change my sex...
I hate pink...
I like Women.
I like Whiskey.
You hid my phone so
you could get my number, right?
Cheap whiskey tomorrow night'?
Can I he honest?
I did find you a hit Weird.
So why did you come to
meet a weirdo'?
Just like the hook at the
end of a TV episode...
which compels you to Watch
the next episode
0111 meeting also ended
somewhat like that
"I Want to he like my mom!"
And than? And than?
So just curiosity.
If it's not a problem
to he like your dad,
then What's the problem
with being like your mom?
They both produced Inc...
Haven't ever heard a man say...
that he Wants to he like
his Mommy.
Didn't Rajiv become like
Indira Gandhi'?
Doesn't Rahul Want to
he like Sonia?
Who was your mom?
Which country was she
the PM of!
She was an artist...
Was she a singer, dancer,
sculptor...
Housewife.
- What?
- She was a housewife.
And than? And than?
Today's episode...
same time, same place?
The shock has given me
severe acidity...
Can't drink tonight.
Ma' am.
What's this?
Dont know.
Came by courier.
Dig one'?
Gelusil?
It's not the alcohol...
it's the curiosity that's
causing the acidity.
Housewives are the
world's greatest artists.
- What's there to be curious'?
- It's not that...
I'm just curious to know
why an INM(B) topper,
instead of taking his
dad's business forward...
dreams to he a housewife
like his mom?
How do you know I'm
from INM(B)'?
Facebook.
It's a small world you know.
But my Facebook page hasn't
been active for ages.
I saw you: picture on a
Facebook friend's page.
Who?
- Neha.
- Dhupia?
Dholakia.
Forget about yesterday...
Yesterday is old news...
I didn't see any
suggestive pictures.
It was tagged,
"Me and my genius topper friend".
So I assumed you guys
were batch mates.
But now I'm 011110115...
Before more curiousity
gives you more acidity...
Eat!
How do you know I
like this pasta?
You: tresses, long and
thick like spaghetti...
Eyes, black like olives...
actually,
eyes not so black...
Nose pointed like
baby corn.
Cheeks flushed like
cherry tomatoes.
Lips made of sliced
bell pepper.
A spicy tongue like
jalapeo.
You are a full on pasta dish.
You're not going to eat
stuffed Indian bread.
Wow Kabir!
I'm floored.
No one has ever seen me
as a vegetable shop!
So romantic.
How can anyone be
romantic with you'?
You Want to arrive fast...
eat fast, talk fast, listen fast...
move ahead fast...
Romance...
happens in slow motion.
Now did you feel something?
Neha...
But somethings fishy.
The pasta's veg,
how can it be fishy'?
If you didn't Want to
he in business,
Why do an MBA?
Before being against something...
one should understand
it fully.
Why are you so
against business?
What is business?
A man has a dream...
To fulfill it he starts
a company.
He employs people to
run the company...
and gives them all a dream
of "moving ahead".
Working day and night,
"moving ahead",
earning millions,
they become blind...
and can't even see that their dreams
Were fulfilled long ago.
Instead of enjoying the
fruits of their labour,
they keep "moving ahead"
like zombies!
Acidity, stress,
heart problems...
Finally they end up in an expensive
private hospital and say...
"Thank God! I can afford
World-class medical treatment."
What? I'm serious!
This mantra of moving ahead
is the most dangerous.
Who are you moving
ahead of!
Where are you going'?
Why are you going'?
In the housewife sector,
there's no "moving ahead" madness.
There's no ranking in
this industry.
So no insecurity,
no acidity
only happiness.
Oh great Saint Kabir.
You're full of shit.
Your goal is to avoid
hard work all your life
I've never heard such a rubbish
philosophy in my life.
Why?
If someone like your dad
does not dream of "moving ahead"...
then how do you become a housewife
and sit at home like your mom?
Mom didn't sit at home
I'm really sorry.
I didn't mean it like that.
How did you mean it than?
What did you mean?
Without a visiting card
or designation...
a person has no value?
Is making a home lesser
than any profession?
It's the biggest bloody
art in the World...
The art of having
no dreams fol yourself.
The art of being happy for others.
The art of happily
sacrificing your identity.
Do you know What is
Mrs.. Bansal's actual name?
She was a pillar for my
big builder dad.
A building falls without support.
Just because she was not
famous or making millions...
she "sat at home and did nothing"?
She was creating a home.
My mother was an artist...
A great artist.
And like every great artist...
she was also very sensitive.
She died early because...
just like you, one day my
father told her...
"What do you do except sit at home!"
My goal is not to
avoid hard work.
But I work hard to avoid
useless goals.
Hey I'm sorry...
I'm really sorry.
I didn't mean it like that.
Hello?
Sorry man!
What do you Want me to do?
Come on now Kabir.
Aren't you a topper?
Please forgive lesser mortals.
Enough Kabir.
Even you: morn wouldn't approve of
such behaviour towards a gill
Sunday tomorrow.
What are you doing'?
I have work in office.
- Take the day off.
- It's tough.
Means you're not sorry.
Hey, this is so cool!
Shit man!
This is the solution to
global Warming!
Why do people buy cats?
Actually maybe fol Women
not so good.
Then-is a lot you don't know.
Yes... Can't tell from that beard
that you're a kid!
Your (one does not sound
like you are sorry.
No, no...
There's a child in everyone,
so it's cool.
You don't Want to go on
the toy train?
It's for ages under 12.
I love trains.
Vintage steam engines,
mini locomotives.
Many late models are here.
Even I have... a full train set!
The world is into space travel.
And you're stuck in
steam engines'?
The romance of trains...
You Won't get it.
You're a robot!
Corporate robot.
Your hardware has no
soft feelings.
You're a corporate psychopath.
If it were up to you,
you'd kill all office-goers.
There is softness.
Touch and see.
Just stone.
Did your mom and dad
feed you granite?
Not mom & dad.
Just mom
I was Z when I lost my dad
in an accident.
He died very young.
So only mom after that.
She married fast,
had a baby fast
became single fast.
So now you know Why
I am "fist-fast".
Hereditary problem
I'm so sorry.
Happens.
After dad died mom
made herself busy.
She became the queen
of social work.
Today she runs a few NGOs
I've always missed having a home
and a perfect family.
I had some softness too...
But now this is me.
Are you single?
Why, do I look double to you?
Don't you have a boyfriend?
On and off...
But no one permanent.
- You scare them away?
- Boys are chicken.
They can't handle a woman
more ambitious than them.
So you're going
to die single?
In an expensive hospital.
But Why are you so curious?
Why? Do you hold the
copyright to he curious?
OK ask me.
- When is you: birthday'?
- 15th April.
What are you saying?
Mine too! 15th April!!
- What'? Don't lie.
- Here look, my I.D.
You think we are twins
separated at birth?
1988!
And you?
Where are you: manners'?
Never ask a woman her
year of birth!
Did you see the 1983 World Cup,
when India won'?
No. I Wasn't horn then.
And the 1987 World Cup'?
When Australia won'?
- No. I was too young.
- That means you are '84 horn
- '85
- You said it, I didn't ask!
Do you like kids?
Yes. But other's.
Don't kids slit your
maternal instincts?
There are so many
kids around.
Why produce one more'?
Afraid'?
Kids and marriage will hijack
your flight to success?
The idea of marriage is good.
It's nice to have someone.
To talk to...
like a special friend...
who you can
cuddle and sleep with!
Your own private happy space.
But a Woman pays too heavy
a price in marriage.
No offense to you: morn, but
the responsibility of a happy home,
is always forced
onto the woman.
However evolved a man is...
a woman's career somewhere
gets compromised.
Marriage is not fol me.
Why? So many Women
manage both Well.
They're super, super women.
So aren't you a super, super,
super woman?
Not at all.
So marry me then!
If you Want to slap me,
then on this cheek please...
I have dental problems this side.
The doctor said I have to
extract my wisdom tooth.
"You're too wise!"
Now Who's fist-fast?
Slow down!
Why should I he the scapegoat
fol you to he a housewife?
Scapegoat?
You Want to move ahead fast,
I don't Want to move ahead at all.
You Want marriage but
you don't Want the domestic hassles
I Want marriage too...
but don't want the office,
career, ambition hassles.
Even out birthdays are the same.
OK I'm three years younger,
but big deal!
We are 100% made for each other.
Unless of coulee you're chicken...
And can't handle
a man without ambition
I'm not in love with you.
Neither am I.
If you're not in love then
why do you want to marry'?
We should get married first...
If we fall in love before...
what will we do after marriage'?
You're breathing is heavy...
You're breaking into a sweat...
You're body is trembling...
You're not in love'?
With my one touch...
your heart was pounding...
You couldn't speak a Wold...
Skipped work to hang
with an aimless dude and...
eat greasy food...
You're not in love'?
Foolish love... Foolish love.
This love of mus.
All topsy-turvy... -
Is there a dog in the house?
Sorry about the mess!
- Hi.
- Hi!
Mom, Kabir
Kabir, mom.
Hi Kabir.
You are her mom?
Are you married?
Say the wold We can change
plans and slope right away!
You only hit on women
older than you'?
Excuse me?
Where are the older women'?
How old are you mister?
Mom We share the same birthday.
But he's 1988.
So he's hitting on you.
No lines. Full circle.
Crazy guy Wants to marry me!
Kabir!
Why do you Want to
commit suicide?
Be single, he happy...
Do something with your life.
Life is too short.
Why Waste it being
someone's husband?
Actually mom, not husband...
he Wants to he my Wife.
What?
Interesting...
Meaning you will eat fol flee?
You Women think like men...
and then call us chauvinists!
If Kia was your son...
and brought home a gill
who Wants to marry and
he a housewife...
Would you ask that gill the
same question?
Point!
But I would ask the
same question even then.
My daughter truly loves you.
Wow mom!
- You're Sherlock Holmes.
- You're not getting it!
What I mean is,
when Women fall in love...
foolish men think We
love only them.
But we love them,
their job, their position...
financial security...
We love the Whole package deal.
But there is nothing to love
ab out you...
except yourself!
You Won't even take
your dad's money.
Which means she really
loves you for you.
Which means...
there must be surely something
special about you.
Oh, your's praising me!
For a second,
I was confused!
But you're OK with this or
not OK with this?
Had sex?
Important before commitment
I'm very excited!
Kia April 15th
Kabir April 15th.
Kia Weds Kabir, also April 15th?
Titanic sank April 15th.
You will never forget the date!
Dad, Kia
Kia, dad.
Sit it's an honour meeting you.
The honour is all mine.
It is the first time he is
introducing me to a friend.
Please sit.
What will you drink?
No, nothing.
I'm fine, thank you.
We are getting married.
What do you do my dear?
- I work at Marion...
- Drivel, peon...
liftman, Watchman...
Anything!
First get him a job...
then do whatever you
Want with him.
How will he look after you?
Just like mom did.
Have you gone mad?
You'll live off a Woman?
You are a man!
If you've forgotten go in, take off
you: underwear and check!
If you don't want to do anything
with you: life then die alone
I'm dealing with it...
It's my misfortune...
Why are you ruining another life'?
A woman is a
man's responsibility.
You should take care of
her, protect her,
fulfill her every need.
When a man becomes a
woman's responsibility
and stays with her as
a househusband...
people call him impotent.
If you're impotent,
quietly stay here.
Why are you broadcasting
this shame'?
MI. Bansal...
Today I am truly proud
of your son.
Despite being horn in this house,
he is the Way he is.
If he had taken over you: business
& made you proud in society,
then you would call
him a "man"...
But fol a Woman...
a real man is one...
who knows he's a man.
Not one who isn't confident of
What's inside his underwear...
and has to shout
from the rooftops...
"I'm a man! I'm a man!
I'm a man!"
Today I consider myself the
luckiest woman in the world.
Because I have a real man
by my side.
Wish you would learn
something from you: son.
One minute...
Didn't buy it with my dad's money...
It's a gift from my uncle.
Underwear check?
Who's first?
Get serious!
We're getting married here!
Congrats!
Mom's...
Happy birthday.
Thank you
I'll go and reheat the tea.
So serious about you: duties
from day one'?
If I don't impress my wife
with my service,
she will kick me out!
I don't drink tea.
Then What do you drink
first thing in the morning?
Other than single malt.
Coffee.
Black, white, filter or instant'?
I am already
very impressed...
you relax I'll make it.
Black, white, filter or instant'?
Black. Filter.
Did you clean up?
No, I opened the Window,
a strong wind blew...
- the place got cleaned up!
- There is a maid to do all this...
- She comes at noon.
- No Women allowed in the kitchen.
This is my kitchen!
Coffee.
Thank you!
- And you: coffee'?
- Tea. Already had two cups.
Bathroom done, jogging
done, shower done...
There! Done praying too.
How's the coffee?
Nice, nice!
Good, good...
All members of this
household are requested...
to always speak the
truth to each other.
This maintains peace and
happiness at home.
Too much milk!
Too bitter!
Good.
Feedback leads to improvement
I'm a tea drinker.
It's the first time I'm making coffee.
How could you hide
such a big truth from me?
If I knew you didn't know
how to make coffee...
I would have never agreed to
this relationship.
Mom, We have been cheated!
Please forgive me.
It will never happen again!
Breakfast? Ornelette,
scrambled, half-fry, French toast?
We don't have breakfast.
Just coffee.
Which is Why you get acidity.
Ornelette, scrambled, half-fry,
French toast...
Gelucil or Digene'?
Stuffed potato parantha,
hot, flied puris...
can't you make?
You Were starving all these days.
Quietly eat whatever I make.
OK
Ornelette...
But it should he fluffy.
Just like in those
French recipe books!
Mummy fol you?
Not had!
What do you know about good and bad'?
It's the first time you're eating breakfast!
Eat something?
Ate long ago.
You thought I'd Wait?
Listen...
This evening...
come home late. No hurry.
What kind of a husband are you?
Aren't you ashamed of sending a woman
alone into this cruel world to earn for her family?
And where's you:
wedding chain'?
Now get lost.
Sorry! I just got really late
I'm surprised you
got up at all today.
Guys, Kia got
married secretly yesterday.
Congratulations!
- Thank you.
- Congratulations!
So Kia, how come
you're at office today'?
Where should I go'?
You just got married yesterday. Don't you
want to take a break? Spend some time at home'?
Rahul, What did you tell me?
You Were in meetings
even on your Wedding day.
So you're the Boss and
my inspiration is my Boss.
Don't remind rue! Sangeeta was waiting
at home with a knife in her hand.
On out first night together.
How do We explain
0111 work to Women?
Same problem...
How do We explain
0111 work to men?
Come over!
Brother, I thought
you were at work!
I am at work.
This is What goes on here?
- I've recorded everything.
- Sorry brother...
This is the first time
I've done this...
Shut up! Stop acting.
Now I'll call the police,
show them a movie.
Please forgive me brother...
I made a mistake,
I'll never do it again!
I'll do whatever you say!
Boyfriend, sex, love...
all are important.
But before using someone's
bed at least ask them!
- Changed the bed-sheet?
- Yes.
How much is your salary?
Ten thousand.
If you use the
bedroom again...
I'll deduct the
Whole ten thousand...
Room charge.
Sorry brother!
Please don't tell Madam...
From tomorrow
12 o'clock won't do...
Sharp 9.
Pick up the broom!
Let's drink cheap Whiskey.
See you in 20 minutes
I've found a new place that sells
expensive Whiskey fol cheap.
Where'?
If you do all this in
flout of me...
I'll also have to find
a lap to sit on.
Some one's been shopping'?
I brought him home
empty-handed...
He'd he roaming naked!
You have to spend some money.
Housewives don't come fol flee.
It's 10.30. Should we
order some food'?
Black lentils, cottage
cheese in butter,
spicy ladyfinger,
yogurt with fried chickpeas...
Indian bread...
And above all, cumin rice.
What Kahit?
Why all this?
We could have ordered...
Food is "ordered" in a hotel...
at home food is "cooked".
But since you are
so fond of ordering...
Ham's the hill...
I need money...
to run the house.
There is nobody like him!
He's got a thousand qualifies...
Every gill Wishes she had
a guy like.
He's the most Wanted man!
Kabir my whole office wants
to meet you.
Tonight! Tonight! Tonight!
What do you think?
We should have a party everyday,
at least then you'll come home early.
What was the need fol
catering, Kia?
I could have cooked.
They are coming to meet you...
and you'll he in the kitchen?
And hey listen!
Don't serve...
Hang around, meet everyone...
Chill.
Just hang loose OK?
Actually...
What have you told
them about me?
What do they think I do?
What do you mean?
Has no one asked you...
the first question everyone
asks after marriage...
What does your husband do?
I said you work from home and...
you're writing a book
or something.
Are you ashamed of me?
Do I embarrass you'?
Kabir...
It's very difficult for people to
understand out trip.
Sorry...
I'm really sorry
I'm so stupid.
Sometimes explaining to
people is such a pain...
It's so difficult that...
out of sheer laziness we just
avoid the topic.
But you know What?
I'm so proud of you
I'm so proud of What We are.
Let's show them today...
What We are.
Lovely house!
You know, your Wife
is going to go places!
- Cheers to that!
- Cheers!
Kia was saying that
you're writing a book?
Hey guys"-
I have an announcement
to make...
Before anyone else asks what
my husband does...
My husband is an artist.
Cheers!
My husband looks after 0111 home
so that I can go places.
My husband takes care of
0111 home, so that...
How do I translate
go places...'?
I can fly.
And he isn't writing any hook...
But someone will definitely write
a hook on him some day.
- So cheers to that guys!
- Cheers!
"I am not embarassed by you"...
You could have whispered
these words in my ear
I didn't ask you for proof!
Is this your mode
of transport?
I'm really sorry!
I don't know how that fell...
Relax.
So Kahit...
If Kia troubles you too much and
you feel like running away...
please come to my house!
No. Not today...
I have a headache.
To hell with your headache!
OK!
Tell Amol to give me the full sketch
of the plans today itself.
Yes today!
We are making a building.
Not some painting!
So?
Did your Wife throw you out?
MI. Singhal's daughter works
in you: wife's office...
Everyone is laughing at me
I'm getting condolence calls!
Have some shame!
Don't Waste your youth on
cooking lentils and rice.
Then-is still time.
Do some real work.
This time will never come hack.
No one will respect you!
Respect is earned by
doing a job Well.
You carry on making buildings
fol respect...
I'm making a home.
One of my signals broke...
Kishen Uncle!
Yes?
There are 2-3 led lights in the
drawer in my cupboard...
Can you please bring them?
I'll get them.
Need money?
Get the ca: ready.
Hey Kia!
- How are you?
Ah the Wives!
- Hello.
- Hello!
Kabir, Kia's better half.
Of course! We've heard
a lot about you.
We Want lots of tips from you.
Tips?
OK, here's the first tip...
Marry an alcoholic...
they will at least
come home!
But a workaholic? Never!
She's always so busy
I told her let's celebrate our
honeymoon before we die.
She said, OK...
I'm going for a marketing conference
to Dubai...
Have you: honeymoon there.
Who takes care of you: house
in you: absence?
I've organised everything.
Mother-in-law will have no trouble...
I've also had CCTV's installed...
You can never trust your
house with the maid.
Which lady are you
flirting with?
I'm honeymooning with everyone's
wives except mine!
Haven't seen your boss
Rahul around.
He has been transferred
to the China office.
Now I report directly
to his boss.
Should We eat?
You cal. Y“ see you in the mom.
Hi baby!
Why did you Wake me up?
You could've taken another
key from the reception.
Sorry!
Come, let's go to sleep.
Why so late?
Michael is 0111 company's
Global Marketing Consultant.
He's from New Yolk.
So just chatting about key
marketing issues.
Very interesting chap.
Sorry!
How could I just
leave halfway?
Sure, I'm right here...
you should've had breakfast
with him as well!
Hello!
Just Watch it!
I was Watching Kia
I'm just you: toy boy, right?
Living off you: pity...
What can I do
except Watch?
What living off pity?
Fool!
We chose this life!
No one forced us.
And I thought We Were
above all this clap!
You didn't even introduce me.
Just dismissed me!
I forgot, that you're also in
the same business...
where it's OK to do
anything to move ahead!
Go. Sleep with him!
You'll get a posting in America.
How date you speak to me
like this?
You're just another cheap
who is pretending
to he evolved!
You showed your true 00101115!
I spoke to a man fol a hit,
and this is What you think of me?
He's a foreigner...
so you're getting more of a complex?
How date you?
Yes I'm a Woman.
Yes I'm a businesswoman. But no...
to move ahead I don't need
to sleep with...
American jealousy...
is good fol Indian health!
Next time We'll try Italian jealousy!
Hey, hey!
Wait wait!
Hey!
Wait Wait Wait!
Happy birthday.
What is this rubbish?
Blood test report is here.
Sugar high. Vitamin D low...
B12 zero...
But Why are you
torturing me?
Her blood runs in you: veins...
you'll have the same problems.
From today priority is health.
Early morning no coffee...
only juice.
Today's menu...
bitter gourd!
Anyway the cup is a
coffee cup. Enjoy!
Sugarfree...
Slim.
Spinach...
Some mole spinach.
Eat...
That's all there is...
Soup and salad.
No oath diet.
At least give me a Whiskey
- there should be some meaning to living!
- Once a week...
that too only if you
follow the diet.
Aren't you eating'?
Are you crazy?
I told you...
learn cooking!
Sugar flee biscuits that
have less sugar...
are priced double of
the sugar biscuits.
Slim milk, which has
less
costs mole than milk
that has mole milk!
Less food is costlier
than more food!
It's all the magic of
marketing!
Actually they should he
paying you mole.
To stay healthy you don't need to
go on an extreme diet.
Why are you Wasting money?
Give us normal food.
Looks like Delhi is safe again!
Come fol a night Walk
with us too!
Look at those legs!
Kahit!
Stop.
You Wanted to see legs, right?
Seeing this macho side of
yours fol the first time...
something is happening to me!
One underwear check is equal to
45 minutes of walking.
Macho?
Yes?
- Is Kia home?
- No she's at work.
- And you are?
- I'm her husband.
And you?
I'm the owner of this flat.
Sorry! Come in.
Please come.
- Can I get you anything? Tea? Coffee?
- No. I'm flue.
Have you come
fol the lent?
You have all the cheques
fol the year, right?
- I've come to return them.
- Did the cheques bounce?
No...
Actually... There's an
emergency
I'll have to sell this house.
And us?
You'll have to vacate...
find another place.
Sit, do you know how hard I have
Worked to make this home?
Finding a house on lent
is such a pain!
Aren't there any flats
available in this building'?
Already checked.
This is so beautiful.
Come Kabir.
Let's play.
- Come on!
- We should buy this house.
Are you mad?
Do you know how much
this place costs?
My full salary will go in paying
the monthly installment...
and mom's salary
from the charity too.
What will We eat?
After a year or two We can
afford it Kabir.
The flat rate will increase
faster than you: salary.
We can never afford to.
Need money! Need money!
Need money!
If I work fol 2-3 years it will
solve the problem.
Should I work or not'?
Work or not'? Work or not'? Work or not'?
If I work I'll dive straight get caught up
in the lat race... become a robot...
go crazy like the rest...
become like dad...
fight everyday with Kia, 0111 home
will he destroyed... Both will die!
Need extra money but everything
should remain the same.
Money money money but
how how how?
How?
To buy the house
We'll have to...
change tracks a little.
And than? And than?
Monthly installment is equal to
Kia's salary. But...
What is monthly expense?
Maintenance...
10,000
Electricity...
3,000...
2,500
Maid... 10,000.
But We need her!
Whiskey 5,000
4,500
Grocery, house expenses...
Kia's shopping, Tam sky...
Entertainment...
Medical emergency.
Credit card, etc...
If we buy the house,
then to run it...
We need 95,000 more
per month.
Who's winning?
Kabir?
It's the first time you're hosting
a kitty party at home...
And so stingy?
Sprouts, soya sticks...
Even the flesh limewater
has no sugar.
Give us samosas, kebabs...
Call fol some heel...
Set the mood!
After all We have to go home
to 0111 husbands' faces!
Spend your day looking at
other faces... Have affairs...
By evening your
mood will he flue!
Will you have an
affair with us?
Not even Hrithik Roshan
can resist you!
Show me!
WOW!
I'm showing you...
Which app is this?
Forever young...
We have to download
this app!
I can give up my life
fol a body like that!
I'll give up all
my fortune!
Give me one 110111
of your life...
and from you: fortune just
Rs. 500 per session...
Can you give me?
Not just the app, I'll download
a Whole new body fol you!
Mummy"-
Sugar level is hack to normal so
chocolate is hack in your life?
What chocolate?
Who was the handsome,
chocolate man?
Why?
Can't I have
handsome friends?
If you feel awkward
around your daughter...
my friend's apartment
is empty...
in case you need some privacy
with your handsome friend.
Handsome friend has an
empty apartment too!
After Kia's dad and...
before this handsome friend,
how many handsome...
- Welcome hack!
Right in time!
Beans and rice is ready.
Kia!
Kia What's happened?
We'll have to sell the house!
We just bought it!
Some problem at work?
I'm finished! I'm finished!
Everything's over.
My dreams, my plans...
my life...
Everything's over!
My career is over!
I don't want to live anymore!
What has happened?
I'm pregnant.
It's all your fault!
- What did I do?
- Who did than?
You should have
been careful!
I'm always careful!
Useless!
- Chill Kia.
- What chill?
It's not you: problem.
The baby is in my stomach!
My life is getting over!
- Calm down! We'll handle this...
- Handle?
What will you handle?
Because you've earned some money,
you can handle anything?
Why should your Wife have any dreams?
Get her pregnant and make her sit at home!
A man's ultimate revenge!
- Took your revenge?
- Shut up Kia!
Bloody useless!
Get lost!
Kia...
What is it?
Pregnancy tests are not
100% accurate...
How accurate are they'?
99%
Ass!
Kia hear me out! Let's try
a few brands. If we Sorry...
If we pass, then we'll go to the
hospital and get properly tested.
If you're definitely pregnant
we'll get an abortion done.
You'll have the abortion?
Is the baby in you: stomach?
Sorry! Sorry!
Take this.
What's this?
All different brands...
Let's test with all.
So many?
Are you mad?
Best of five...
Positive!
1-0:
2-0!
I've already done one!
Chill! Chill!
Next...
There's some problem...
- It's showing negative.
- This is the right one! Yes!
I knew it...
You're not pregnant!
This is the right one.
- This is also negative.
- Z-Z! Yes!
I knew it! I knew you're
not pregnant!
Hey Kia!
Negative! Negative!
3-2!
How can you ever think
I'll stop your life?
- Now why'?
- What if it's 3-3'?
4-2 a
Negative!
I can't believe this!
Whatever the problem...
it's not Your's or Mine...
it's Ours.
We're in this together.
Don't take off on me
like that...
Ever!
I'm sorry baby!
Then-is a product launch
next Week...
so I just panicked!
Forget that product.
If this product had launched...
who would pay the
monthly installment?
My problem is bigger than
you: problem!
Now come. There's you: favourite
beans and rice for dinner. Come on.
You marketing guys
don't understand.
You: emotional ad campaign
won't do!
The pressure of sales
is on me.
We need an offer.
To boost the sales,
Rs. 20 off immediately!
You made an offer of
Rs. 10 off just 4 months ago!
You sales guys will
kill the brand!
- There will be no brand without buyers...
- Sit!
This is short term thinking!
Rs. 20 off is less.
We should give 50% off.
What?
- But not fol Women.
- Meaning?
50% off...
if the men come to buy.
Kia!
You've lost it?
Which man buys
cooking oil?
Maybe in your house...
If We tell Women...
this offer is only for men...
all of them will force their
men to go to the stores.
Their love for the brand
will increase...
because thanks to the brand, their
lifelong dream is being fulfilled...
of getting men to shale the
responsibility of running the house.
Why should caring fol the
health of the family...
only be the wife's duty'? Men must
share that responsibility too.
The house is in his name...
so shouldn't he be doing
some housework too'?
And one mole thing,
maybe because of this...
your Wife also will start
liking you mole!
Brilliant!
Kia this is a
breakthrough idea!
The whole Saffola range
should have this offer!
Kabir...
I got promoted to
Vice President Marketing!
Here he is!
From today onwards
training...
- stops!
- What?
Take care of you:
own bodies.
- What do you mean?
- Why?
Wife's status is rising.
Mother-in-laws status is changing.
Too many responsibilities now...
no time!
Don't do this Kabir,
you're my life!
We had a target of 15 kilos,
only 6 has been achieved!
We need you Kabir!
But I don't need the money!
- My god! You can't do this!
- Please!
But... I Won't take money.
- So no then.
- OK, OK!
- Bye.
- Kia Wait!
So late!
Have you eaten?
Too tiled.
How was your day?
- It's Sunday.
- So?
Don't you know What
Sunday means?
Big review meeting tomorrow.
I'll have to go to office.
Miss it!
' Can't!
' can!
Can't!
For a woman to make a name in the
corporate world at such a young age...
is still very rare Kia.
It's a big achievement
I think it's equally
difficult for the men.
Come on it's much
tougher on us.
We have to excel both at
the office and at home.
I only focus on my work...
My husband takes
care of the house.
Wow!
Is he fol real?
Wish everyone had a
husband like yours
I'd really like to
meet him!
Kia What is this? Why did
you give them my number?
- It's a small interview. No big deal.
- I don't like all this! Why are We doing this?
I will benefit. Your interview
will give me mole publicity.
OK bye now I have to go!
Kabir thank you fol
letting us into your life.
You have a beautiful home!
- Thank you.
- When did you decide...
that you would take care
of the house full time '.7.
The first time I came to this
house and saw it's condition...
I decided that the "men" in
this house needed a "Woman".
So can we say that in you:
relationship, Kia is the man'?
No...
Kia is a Woman,
and I am a
but I understand
you: confusion.
Homemaker means you're a "she",
having a career means you're a "he"...
According to "Indian tradition".
True, hut Kia is a very successful Woman
& you are dependent on her financially...
Does you: ego ever hurt'?
Do you feel jealous?
So you're saying that...
all those women who are homemakers are
jealous of their husband's success?
Using their money to run
the house hurts their ego'?
If Women don't feel it,
Why do you think men will feel...
jealous... have an ego?
Maybe men's upbringing,
genetic difference...
Of course.
We are different...
Which is why I don't wear a bra &
she doesn't have a beard.
But genes don't say that
a bra can't go to work...
or that a beard can't
run the house.
My "she" is proving
to the world...
that she's no less
than a "he"...
And this "he" is proving
to the world...
that he's no less
than a "she"!
The Constitution of India gives
every citizen the freedom of choice.
She and he have the freedom
to choose what they want to do.
We chose this life. Why is it
breaking news to you'?
Kia!
I saw your husband's
"He-She" interview...
Damn cool!
What a dude your
husband is!
For a minute even I was
influenced by his words!
You're a very
lucky gill!
You: husband is a very
progressive man.
Yes. All companies should
recruit more women
I wish more of out men were like him.
He's from INM(B), right'?
Kia, your husband's trending!
Let's get hack to work guys.
Hi Ma'am...
I saw your interview...
- Thank you!
- I loved What you Were Wearing!
You've become an
overnight stat!
Saw the interview?
I gave you so much publicity!
Me? You Were
praising yourself!
Anyway you looked hot!
It was a question of your reputation!
I did the make-up and lighting myself.
What did you mean "condition
of the house" before you came?
Did we live in the
gutter before'?
That was a joke...
A true joke.
And What was that...
"She" is proving to the world that
she's no less than a "he"...
That was a compliment!
What do you think?
That my life's
is to show people that
I'm no less than a man?
I'm not proving anything
to anyone, OK?
I just Want to he the best
at What I do.
She finds faults
even in compliments!
You said something?
I saw your son on T.V.
But Women's Day is
next month...
What was he
doing on T.V.'.7.
Sit, he speaks very Well.
- Did he say anything about me?
- No sit...
He didn't even take
your name.
Thank God...
else 0111 apartment
prices would fall!
- Hello?
- Hi, is this MI. Kabir Bansal?
Yes, speaking.
Sit We would like you to talk in
0111 Ted X Program.
- What is this? I'm starving!
- Sorry!
What will you have?
Just order anything!
Hello?
Sit, we're doing a cookery show...
- Don't you think'?
- Clutter-breaking idea, sit!
Sit I know it's
very interesting...
but I don't think he'll do it.
Television is going to die.
Who will Watch T.V. with
so many ads?
They should ban ads!
When-is mom?
Some NGO seminar
or something.
Drink?
You Won't believe it...
my boss Wants to
cast you in an ad.
Excuse me?
Don't Worry...
I said no.
Which ad?
Saffola!
Saffola?
Saffola...
Actually Kia it's
a good idea.
You: last "offer" idea for men
was such a hit...
Actually...
it's a great idea!
How long will we
stereotype women in ads'?
Ads influence society, right?
Change ads,
change society!
You'll do an ad?
Kia, I Want Kabir to give 0111
Marketing & Sales team...
an inspirational talk. Just
an informal evening session.
He's such an interesting man.
I'm sure people will love it!
Kabir?
Hale'!?
You're really enjoying you:
new life, aren't you'?
I really enjoyed
coming to you: office.
But how do you
work there'?
I Wasn't talking about
this evening.
What do you mean?
I mean...
all these talks and speeches...
At first I found these interviews &
talks on gender equality very irritating.
But after seeing the initial
Response, I started.
If I can do some good,
then Why not?
What good are you doing?
By sharing out lives...
if someone else's life
gets better, then why not'?
I thought I was the marketing person,
and you didn't like marketing...
You are marketing
your life!
0111 life!
Not my life.
My life is not so different.
So many women work...
You're the different animal!
And anyway who are
you helping?
You think that centuries of
injustice done to Women...
can he wiped clean in a
second by your example?
It's the men, not the Women
who are benefiting from this.
Inspired by you, men think they can
sit at home & become stats!
If you don't want to work...
why encourage others
to be useless.
That you find happiness
in my happiness.
Is not necessary in love...
If 0111 paths don't meet...
does not mean We are apart...
This is love, not duty...
I have some good news.
We Want to send you to New Yolk
for a management pro gramme.
It's a fabulous one month
pro gramme.
Would you like to go'?
Everything OK?
Yes sit. I'll go
I'm already depressed!
How can you both leave
me all alone...
and go to the U.S.
fol a month?
Very mean!
What alone? I'm not going
I'm just joking...
What's happened to you Kabir?
He's become famous mom...
- He doesn't have dates.
- What?
Everything stops from today.
What?
Anyway...
the country's youth is Watching
this useless example...
and getting corrupted!
What?
How can I leave you in
this condition?
What's happened to me?
Anything can happen. Anyway my job
is to take care of the house...
not to travel the world!
I'm sorry...
For what?
Why Won't you come?
What will I come and
do there for a month'?
You'll he able to
stay without me?
You'll he busy...
Instead of living there without you
it's better if I stay here without you.
At least I can look
after mom.
I Want to he useful.
Then I Won't go too.
Don't go!
But I've already accepted...
and it's a great
opportunity to learn.
So go...
I didn't mean What I
said in the cat
I mean What I'm
saying now.
You do your work,
I'll do mine.
Anyway you feel that
I don't do anything.
If I come to America
with you and enjoy...
even I'll feel that
I'm useless!
I don't know how to convince you...
This is love, not duty...
Does not mean I desire you any less.
Times have changed a hit,
But I'm the same, my love...
How do I make you understand
I don't know how to make you happy
But I Want to see a smile on your face.
This is love, not duty...
That you find happiness
in my happiness.
Is not necessary in love...
That you find happiness
in my happiness.
Is not necessary in love...
If 0111 paths don't meet...
does not mean We are apart...
Where are you going all
dressed up like a stud?
To focus on my
present life...
I had made my past
out of focus...
But now my past is
calling out to me.
After many years then-is a
reunion of all the MBA robots.
Shall I go?
If you come home early
sleep outside!
So you learned
how to cook?
Yes, completely!
- Hi Kabir!
- Hi Neha.
- How's Kia?
- She's good. Very good.
When Z people have
a scene in college...
and they lose touch...
and meet after
many years...
that moment guys...
is pule sex!
Here! Sex done'?
- What are you drinking?
- I Want to get drunk!
I Want to have shots!
Kabir...
You gave me a big
complex in college...
Now that I'm Worth
400 million dollars, and single...
you still make me
feel like a loser!
What did I do?
You're the one who is in every
Woman's dream even after marriage!
You've become a film director but
still didn't bring an actress along.
Your life is no less than a film.
How much fol the copyrights?
- Kahit?
- Yes?
Will you come to
Mumbai fol me?
Why is your husband
in Delhi?
No in Paris. Ass!
My channel is doing a big
pro gramme for Women's Day...
I stopped doing all that...
Please do it fol me?
Just one day! Please?
How many times can I say the
same thing? Anyway it's Women's Day...
Women should speak fol
the benefit of Women to Women!
For Women to benefit
men should speak to men.
No, you find yourself
another man
I've committed...
I'll he badly screwed!
Just one day...
Please!
(Kabir: History says, in the stone ages
men hunted and Women in caves cooked...)
No one checked how
many men cooked...
and how many Women hunted!
If you miss 1 match out of 121
it Won't make any difference...
Today's Women's Day, sit with your
Woman and listen to this boy!
If we reversed the roles,
then what?
The Woman's job would he hunting...
the man's job, cooking!
Only their responsibilities
would have been swapped.
Men would have Remained men...
Women would have Remained Women...
Sex would have been just as good!
Yes, but today We...
would not be celebrating
Women's Day...
but Men's Day instead!
History must have been written
by a man!
His-tory...
The clue is in the wold itself,
His Story!
Does anyone know
Her Story?
- Who's this fellow?
- He's a man!
I can see that.
The men who discovered the Hindi language
knew this about this mistake...
In Hindi grammar,
"cooking" is a masculine gender...
So cooking is
male territory.
"Working" is a feminine gender...
Female territory!
Fact is...
we ale speaking one language,
and living another.
He takes care of his home
so his Wife can fulfill? her dreams.
Good!
Good? Could you have
ever done this?
Yes, Why not?
Rubbish! If I had
continued my acting work...
would you have taken
care of the house?
Absolutely. If that was
your dream.
You can't boil a glass of
water on you: own!
We would have got a cook.
Does he have kids?
- That's not the point!
- That's the point...
That's the big point Jaya!
When did I stop you
from Working?
It was your choice!
Exactly. It was my choice
because I had no other choice!
What are you saying!
I would have happily
looked after the house!
sure!
Amitahh Bachchan cooking
in the kitchen...
and Jaya Bachchan happily
Waving to her fans every Sunday!
You would have
been OK with it?
Yeah.
Why not?
So easy to say it.
Can't rewind life!
What do I do?
What do you Want
me to do?
- I Want to meet this boy.
- Who? This guy?
- Yeah.
- Why?
I like him.
Just look at him!
At this age a new threat!
Hi. You coming?
Corning where?
So Why did you call?
I just called to say...
I called to say I'm meeting
Amitahh Bachchan & Jaya Bachchan!
What?
I'm in Mumbai.
What are you doing
in Mumbai?
Then-is a Women's Day
seminar...
Another speech...
Started again?
I thought you Wasn't going
to do all this!
This is Why you didn't
come with me, right?
Anyway. Good...
meet mole people.
Kia I'm meeting Ami...
Yeah flue.
Take care.
This is fol Kia.
Thank you!
What wrong did I
do to you'?
I'll have to heat her
lectures fol days!
Kia, 20 missed calls?
Mom...!
What happened?
Her BP was very low.
She collapsed.
She was trying to
call you.
She called Kia,
Kia called me...
We had to rush her here.
Kia was saying...
she'll catch some flight via
Zurich and leach by tonight.
- Hello?
- Where are you'?
Kia you've landed...
I'm almost there!
I'm already in the
bloody hospital!
Flight arrived early?
- Swiss air was supposed to...
- I came by Lufthansa.
- Why didn't you call me?
- Call you?
The whole world was
trying to call you!
Why did you come hack?
Go give mole speeches!
Nothing’s happened. Mom is flue. You
didn't have to leave work & rush here
I came. I'm here!
You Were not here!
What is this sudden trip
to become famous'?
Why do you suddenly want to
show the world how great you are'?
You left home to tell the world
how well you run a home'?
You're a bloody fraud!
This is a hospital.
Please go outside.
Kia! I Went to meet
Amitahh Bachchan...
Did mom's blood pressure know that
you Were with Amitahh Bachchan?
If Amitahh Bachchan knew
that my mom was dying...
and you Were telling stories of
being a "cool husband"...
he would have thrown you out!
My phone was on silent...
there Were no flights out.
I took the first...
You're living off my money and you
want to show the world how great you are'?
OI is it that because
I'm older than you...
you're doing me a favour
by living with me.
Kia listen...
Now that you're on T.V. and
a social celebrity...
you: "homemaker" & "don't want to
move ahead" act is over'?
Kia...
You don't want to progress!
The joke of the century!
You are the cheapest, slimiest...
most manipulative
man in this world.
Why are you living off Inc...
when you are the heir
to millions?
Why? Why? Why?
You used me!
I'm such a fool!
It was pule strategy!
You plotted this hit by hit!
It was all a set-up!
Nothing was a coincidence...
from the Chandigarh-Delhi
flight until now...
Was it really you: dead
mother's birthday that day'?
Brilliant game, brilliant
bloody game!
You proved that you're an
MBA topper.
What a business plan!
I'll become a hem not by
inventing anything...
not by becoming yet another
millionaire, not by anything. Just...
by doing nothing!
Without doing anything I will
leave my mark in the world.
You are an artist...
The World's biggest
con artist!
You used me to laugh at your dad...
to laugh at the whole bloody world...
Kia...
Kia, let's go hack.
Mom is alone.
My mom. My home
I'll take care of it.
Dear Kia...
We really missed you.
Kabir told us a lot about you
I'm truly, truly proud of you.
I know the world is
celebrating Kabir today...
but without a Kia,
a Kabir cannot exist.
Every Woman Wishes fol
a husband like this...
but very few have the courage
to love such a man.
It takes a lot fol a
man to he a Kahit...
But it takes a lot mole fol
a Woman to he happy...
with a man like Kabir.
You are a big inspiration!
I wish the world would
have more women like you, Kia.
God bless you!
That you find happiness...
in my happiness.
Is not necessary in love...
If 0111 paths don't meet...
does not mean We are apart...
When-is Kabir?
Kia!
I'm so cheap mom!
I hate myself I.
I felt jealous of him!
How can I he jealous
of Kabir mom?
I love him, I love him
mole than my life!
Calm down Kia!
He got a little attention...
and I couldn't handle it!
I feel so small mom!
I'm feeling so small.
How can I he
insecure of him?
Kabir loves you too.
Not once did he say that
I wasn't at home either.
And I abused him fol not
being there fol just one night!
What happened Kia?
This is love, not duty...
I really didn't mean what I said!
I didn't mean what I said morn...
Of coulee you meant it.
Else you Wouldn't have said it.
I didn't mean What I said
I really love Kabir!
Love is not the problem...
There is no problem
between Kabir and you.
Infant, this is not a
husband-Wife, man-Woman...
or... What is that...
not even a "he-she" problem...
This is a basic issue between a
homemaker and the person who earns...
Whether it's a "she" or a "he"...
Unfortunately, the world only sees the
person who earns in the relationship
because of which the person
gets used to the attention.
It's natural!
No one notices the homemaker...
Slowly, even the earning member
stops noticing the homemaker.
When the world by chance
notices the homemaker...
then natal-ally, the
homemaker feels a bit nice...
and the earning member
feels a bit shaken.
Hey! I'm the hem!
How can the supporting actor
equal to me!
But I'm not like that mom!
You are exactly like that!
We are all I'.ike that.
W eke human beings'.!
But you know What is so
beautiful about you?
You don't Want to he like that.
Credit card used for
Vistara Airlines... 5,000'?
Kahit!
Hello? Yes?
Can you tell me if MI. Kabir Bansal
is traveling on any of your flights today?
His Wife is dying!
It's an emergency!
If I knew the flight number
Why would I he calling you?
What is UK246?
Chandigarh?
You Were in Chandigarh
to buy Chandigarh?
No.
My friend had a break-up...
I was there for rnoral support
I'm sorry!
I'm really sorry.
I was just missing
my husband.
But I'm OK now...
He loved his mom a lot.
During take off and landing...
he would hold her hand
tightly like this.
Yes sit?
Ma'am can you get this
lady her husband please?
I lost him somewhere!
Found him!
Over!
What's over?
Murder.
- Whose?
- Yours!
I smashed you, bashed you,
chopped your body into pieces...
and took my revenge.
Peace!
Folded my hands, pleaded, got down
on my knees, asked for forgiveness.
Got it!
Peace!
But Why did you come
after me so quickly?
I can understand if my
friend was a "she"...
If you: friend was a "she"...
this plane Wouldn't have
lauded in Chandigarh.
You could have shown up
before hoarding...
We could have saved money
on the return ticket!
We will come hack by train.
I Want to feel...
the romance of trains!
Happy birthday m you!
Today on your birthday...
- a gift...
- I don't Want anything dad.
Thank you fol coming.
Just enjoy a meal
cooked by your son.
Who's giving you anything?
On the occasion of my
daughter-in-law's birthday...
I've come to ask her fol a gift.
To take my company forward...
I need a CEO.
A CEO...
who after I'm gone...
can take over my company.
Me?
I think I'm too
small fol this...
You're very talented.
I keep track of all your work!
Cheers!
Is he offering me dowry
in the middle of the night?
He's making sure
the family business...
is being handed over
to the right family member.
Are you interested in
charity work?
Charity? What charity?
Till today I thought that behind
every successful
there is a Woman.
And you: son proved that...
behind a successful
Woman there is a man.
No, no...
You daughter has
proved that...
there needs to he a
successful Woman...
in flout of every
unsuccessful man!
When did you last do an
underwear cheek?
What's that?