good evening everybody my name is Nevada
Thomas it is really nice to see you all
for a girl with many dreams aspirations
and ambitions the one thing that I was
fighting against was the lack of time
but I think it's safe to say we all wish
we had more of that time as our lives
and everything around us seems to be
moving seems to be like somebody played
a tape recorder press the fast-forward
button and left it that way it's all
moving at such a rapid pace right so it
is only fair to us to pause breathe and
take a moment to think about the past
the good we faced the bad we experienced
but mind you when you move forward and
like the only baggage that you would
want to carry forward should be the good
because it would be an unpleasant case
otherwise as I sat down to think about
how to brainstorm and compile everything
that I wanted to talk about today there
was one moment it was more of the
revelation when I realized if one 23
year old had so many things to talk
about so much to say imagine the kind of
life experiences and stories you would
get to hear from people around the world
it was really exciting to think about it
let me take you through mine now
so I was born and raised in the
beautiful China City but my roots go
back to a small village in it called a
duel in irritating Kerala though I was
raised schooled everything in thumb in
Urdu my connect with my homeland Kerala
is very strong in fact it's as strong as
my love for Kappa fish curry for Emporia
and Shia is there are Mele alleys here
you will know exactly what I'm talking
about it's deep trust more but I think I
am privileged to say I believe that I'm
equally a Telugu am I now as much as I
am a Malayalee
and a Tamilian and this because this
cultural integration is what makes me
call anywhere home and I believe this
cultural integration is is
necessary for us to grow better rolling
back a couple of years now we're getting
into the the topic I'm going to share
with you a couple of my life experiences
what I went through and whatever I am
today is because of all these
experiences I had so I would like to
share it with all of you so rolling back
a couple of yours the word school the
word school resonated with an album to
me like a photo album of Polaroids
flashing in front of my eyes I have very
vivid memories of what school meant to
me I faced the camera first when I was
eight years old and since then believe
it or not I have been to school
sometimes visited school by visit I mean
literally just visited school three or
four times three or four days a month
honestly that's how much I've been there
there are I I think definitely my
teachers must have seen chief guests
repeat themselves to events more than
I've actually been in school but going
to work acting you know on longer
schedules and then coming back to
sitting in class being attentive
completing class works being on par with
where the rest of the class was was very
taxing sometimes I would also want to
give up removing all the makeup before I
fly to bed not the fair I could think
about it or realize you know the the
struggle with all this this had already
become my life so as a kid I remember I
wanted to take a moment to decide on few
things before I proceeded forward I
wanted to draw a line between work and
study that's what I wanted to do it
sounds like a very very simple idea but
trust me when I say this it required a
battalion a battalion of people to
execute I needed my teachers my
principal my friends from workplace my
friends from school my producers my
directors all my technicians and my
family more than anything
and today when I look back and think
about it I have been more than blessed I
feel like I've been blessed more than
required to have had them all in fact my
school was so supportive my principal
brother George was so supportive of me
going to act that the three or four days
that I would go to go to school he would
look at me and be like oh no Bates are
you're here when are you going back to
work I was like let me and my timing was
so off the four or five days are like
that I got to be in school was when I
had my math test
don't even ask me about it I've also
played stunts where I I have fever and I
I want my mom to take me back home just
once but yeah I have done that sadly
school was school was abundant school
was what set my foundation the base of
the base for me was is it's just it's so
strong and I can so happily say that my
character and my personality anything to
deal with the development of my
personality I owe it to my school and I
can't thank or talk enough about the
importance of holistic education that I
received from school this one memory is
so vivid in my mind where the fact that
I the announcement of me receiving my
first ever award for my first film in
Malayalam which is called where the
other barrier I had received a kerala
state award for it and the work the
person I got to know that from was
brother George my principal I was in the
school ground practicing long jump for
something for the sports tape all muddy
and dirty and there's the student who
come says who spells calling you
what do you instantly think I'm like
what did I do now I behave that was okay
did I do something wrong
so from point A to point B that's what
I'm I'm thinking about so I go to his
office and then he turns on the
television tunes into a channel
and he simply said who won so I saw my
name scrolling down with the picture em
honestly that moment it hit me so hard
that rather than feeling accomplished or
satisfied everything around me became
muted it got really quiet and I thought
that appreciation came just at the right
moment in my life when I almost took it
synonymous to wanting to show my
gratitude towards all the people who
helped me get to that point my principal
my family everybody came to my mind at
that point it was just so special and
that episode ended with you know like in
my mind it was like all my teachers from
graduating me and seeing them celebrate
and seeing them feel so joyous about me
achieving something was validation to me
that all that hours and days of hard
work doing what I loved doing was
absolutely worth it so from then on I
was happily studying away till there was
one moment where I I think I can speak
confidently for all of you there's that
one moment in your school life when we
feel something completely brand new this
is exactly after I finished my twelfth
grade which for some reason at this
point in time it feels like a danger
zone that's how it that's how it's made
to be felt like a danger zone when I
cross that that that stayed I was posted
with a very very very difficult question
what next honestly this is how it was in
my mind the room got extremely dark
there's a focus light on you all your
relatives start becoming active again
even distant once your parents are alert
your siblings if you have younger ones a
sister or a brother he or she is
suddenly looking up up at you thinking
what are you going to do who are you
going to be what do you become
what do you want to become who do you
want to be in life look though this is
an exercise just go home and say this
question three times then you'll want to
sit down because I've never been able to
answer this question who do you want to
become what do you want to become in
life
it's an incredibly heavy question which
I feel requires a lot of thinking and a
lot more living to actually figure out
so at that point I had to choose between
walking a trodden path or an untrodden
path either you work in films or you
study something you specialize in some
field and become something but I chose
to walk in between yeah I did back then
I don't know I was just I I remember
telling my parents Amma daddy I want to
I want to work as I'm studying and I
remember them looking at each other and
they were like well if you can manage
then we don't have a problem with it
because honestly this decision was taken
by me honestly because I couldn't
imagine myself doing just one of it
because most of my life I've been
working and studying together so I just
couldn't think about doing choosing one
from that point on everything moved so
fast
it moved literally like this I moved on
from wanting to study aerospace
engineering to joining University to
study five years of architecture don't
ask me how that happened that happened
so when this fairy tale of school life
was just ending the actual picture came
into my life when I started college
College came in like a royal entry it
had a royal entry call it sort of feels
like us going to watch a Rajinikanth
film first day first show you have this
unexplainable hi you don't know what
you're feeling you suddenly feel like an
adult you you know you're given up
you're given a car you can drive
yourself to college
you know school though it's only cycling
and auto man
maybe my van driver who drove me for 14
years and suddenly you have a car
you have a place to park your car and
then you no longer wearing uniforms it's
so exciting you know you you feel like
you're an adult and you have
responsibilities and honestly no money
can ever buy the experiences that I had
or the lessons I learned during college
the five years of me studying an
institution and moving around with the
people there
it taught me more about myself than
anything or anybody could have ever
taught me
College was fun but architecture did not
serve it easy for me or for any of my
classmates for that matter I was visibly
struggling at this point I was I I had a
lot of struggles with having to manage
minimum attendance required to appear
for exams struggling with trying to
trying really hard to perform well
struggling with completely completing
designs on time struggling to be on par
with where the rest of the class was
this was extremely taxing it was but
while also listening to strip readings
and there were a lot of narrations
happening which I would okay at one
point so that I can work on those films
when I had my semester vacation so this
is how my pattern in college life was
all this was happening but the real
struggle was inside me I was constantly
at war with my mind I was struggling
with exaggerated thoughts I was fighting
against stress more than the physical
exhaustion I was fighting against stress
strain fear doubt overthinking
procrastination and also extreme
self-criticism
all these were emotions I was not
prepared to fail
I was not prepared to handle nobody
taught me in school or anywhere to to
learn how to handle these things and all
I would do is sometimes just break down
and cry would that make me feel better
sometimes but not really I would not
know what to do when I was in a point
that way it was extremely difficult now
when I think about that face between
2013 and 2018 happily thinking about it
I also think how did I even get through
how did I get through that at that point
how did I go through from semester to
semester how did I even do that I think
about it and there were a couple of
things that came to my mind was it the
way I was so warmly welcomed into a
whole new industry the Telugu industry
which happened during my second year of
college or was it the kind of
appreciation that I and my team received
for films like gentlemen and then the
quarry and everything that followed
wasn't the radical thinking of my mom
and the constant support she gave me was
it the difficulty with which my father
moved so far away from family to work
for the family earn money for the family
keep us in good shape while he missed us
so much and still worked with so much of
conviction was it seeing my brother live
his life like there's no tomorrow so
happy was it seeing my friends though
they were having struggles of their own
working extremely hard toiling
rigorously to make sure that they
accomplished their dreams while helping
me out - or was it the hand of God that
was constantly there beside me guiding
me through every step of the way and
always whispering in my ears that you're
not alone yes I believe it was all of
this but most importantly it was the
small decision that
I made to have little faith in myself
that I could do it no matter what I
could do it it seemed like a very very
simple idea
but it actually worked
I just thought this is my life I wanted
this I should be prepared from all of
this because I chose this the decision
was mine so no matter how difficult it
gets nobody is going to help you nobody
is going to be able to help you but
yourself so when I pass out of college
honestly I came out I believe I came out
much stronger I came out to be a
stronger person mentally and physically
I started appreciating myself more I
accepted the bodily changes I had
through time I understood the value and
importance of constructive criticism and
I started seeing beauty and flaws
because trust me I realized more than
ever that we are perfect just the way we
are we don't realize it we are perfect
just the way we are and boys and girls
please don't bend your knee to satisfy
societal standards live your life
because that's yours and no matter how
much you wish you got help no matter how
much you wish that this moment just fast
I closed my eyes in this moment just
pass it will never happen because those
things only happen in movies you know
they really don't happen into your life
so as long as you start believing in
believing in yourself these things will
not magically happen and through all
this I realize the importance of people
and the importance of interaction I
needed people you know people are what
people are who made me get through all
this time they helped me a lot every
doctor needs a patient every police
needs a case every climber needs a
mountain every speaker needs an audience
likewise
every actor needs an audience like every
speaker needs a listener every actor
needs an audience and me being an actor
I feel extremely privileged to be able
to be so many different kinds of people
because that is my dream we human beings
are gregarious in nature no man is an
island we cannot live in an in an
alienated society so I believe the
choices I make
I wanted the choices that I make to have
a rippling effect in the society but not
a crippling effect I wanted to make sure
that I am different people that was my
dream that is my dream I want to be so
many different characters I want to have
I want to portray the shades that we all
experience and we wish we experience
from good to the bad to fictional
everything and I all this while
everything that I was saying my life
story is not great my life story is not
extraordinary and I did not do great
things but the only thing that I did and
that I'm happy about is that I just
would not quit I would not want to stop
trying so I want to portray people that
way you know and the medium this is my
dream so the medium I choose to voice
out my expression is cinema and I will
always continue doing that thank you
[Applause]